const QUESTIONS = [
  {
    question: "In the year 1900 in the U.S. what were the most popular first names given to boy and girl babies?",
    a: "William and Elizabeth",
    b: "Joseph and Catherine",
    c: "John and Mary",
    d: "George and Anne",
    answer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "When did the Liberty Bell get its name?",
    a: "When it was made, in 1701",
    b: "When it rang on July 4, 1776",
    c: "In the 19th century, when it became a symbol of the abolition of slavery",
    d: "None of the above",
    answer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of the following items was owned by the fewest U.S. homes in 1990?",
    a: "Home computer",
    b: "Compact Disk Player",
    c: "Cordless phone",
    d: "Dishwasher",
    answer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "In 1990, in what percentage of U.S. married couples did the wife earn more money than the husband?",
    a: 8,
    b: 18,
    c: 38,
    d: 58,
    answer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "During the 1980s for six consecutive years what breed of dog was the most popular in the U.S.?",
    a: "Cocker Spaniel",
    b: "German Shepherd",
    c: "Labrador Retriever",
    d: "Poodle",
    answer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "In 1985, five percent of U.S. households had telephone answering machines. By 1990 what percentage of homes had answering machines?",
    a: "10%",
    b: "15%",
    c: "31%",
    d: "51%",
    answer: "c"
  },
  {
    question: "The first black American pictured on a U.S. postage stamp was who?",
    a: "Frederick Douglass",
    b: "Booker T Washington",
    c: "Louis Armstrong",
    d: "Joe Louis",
    answer: "d"
  },
  {
    question: "What did the \"D\" in \"D-Day\" stand for?",
    a: "doom",
    b: "day",
    c: "Dwight (Eisenhower)",
    d: "Dunkirk",
    answer: "b"
  },
  {
    question: "Which of these characters turned 40 years old in 1990?",
    a: "Charlie Brown",
    b: "Bugs Bunny",
    c: "Mickey Mouse",
    d: "Fred Flintstone",
    answer: "a"
  },
  {
    question: "Before becoming George Bush's Secretary of Defense, what was Dick Cheney's position?",
    a: "congressman from Wyoming",
    b: "governor of New Hampshire",
    c: "secretary of defense under Ronald Reagan",
    d: "monkey",
    answer: "a"
  }
];